

789 Tenth Avenue, Fort Worth, TX 35555 m.raymondson@emai Lcom (222) 222-2222 A diligent construction project manager who has worked for over nine years in the industry. Proven ability to complete projects in a cost-efficient manner without cutting corners or sacrificing safety considerations. Able to negotiate contracts and handle budgeting while overseeing multiple job sites. Can adjust projects to account for adverse weather and other disruptive circumstances.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CONSTRUCTION PROJECT

MANAGER

Fort Worth Industries, Fort Worth. TX I October 2015-Present

- Manage crews up to 200 workers in size on commercial building construction and renovation projects
- Work with a revolving set of clients, overseeing 30+ projects annually
- ♦ Complete permitting process before projects begin
- Select and manage contractors for specialty work
- Develop and monitor project budgets

SITE SUPERINTENDENT

Arlington Solutions, Arlington, TX I July 2011 - September 2015

- Ensured compliance with federal, state and local safety regulations
- Oversaw placement of signs and barriers
- Purchased supplies and equipment as needed
- Implemented maintenance and cleaning programs for equipment
- Reviewed and reported on work of contractors and subcontractors

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN CONSTRUCTION ENGINEERING

Texas Institute Of Engineering, Houston, TX | September 2 005 - June 2009

MASTER OF SCIENCE IN CONSTRUCTION MANAGEMENT

Fort Worth Business Academy I ort Worth I September 2009-June 2011

KEY SKILLS

- Correcting unsafe behaviors and other hazards on job sites
- Creating schedules and budgets with software such as Procore and Autodesk Construction Cloud
- ♦ Client and worker communication
- Navigation of permitting processes

CERTIFICATIONS

Construction Management Certification, U.S.
Construction Management Association, 2016